[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 6, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "gun", "murders", "were", "there", "in", "Britain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "How many great white sharks --", "answer_tokens": ["How", "many", "great", "white", "sharks", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Why do you want to deport me?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "want", "to", "deport", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well, we did it as a way to bring attention to the fact that we have all of these foreigners and the Russian government, the official Chinese government.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "did", "it", "as", "a", "way", "to", "bring", "attention", "to", "the", "fact", "that", "we", "have", "all", "of", "these", "foreigners", "and", "the", "Russian", "government", ",", "the", "official", "Chinese", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "You finished?", "question_tokens": ["You", "finished", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Yes, I am finished.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "am", "finished", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["74 percent"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "JJ", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Do you know?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "There were about 11,458, and about 74 percent of those were gang related, gang bangers shooting each other.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "were", "about", "11,458", ",", "and", "about", "74", "percent", "of", "those", "were", "gang", "related", ",", "gang", "bangers", "shooting", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 95, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain last year?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "gun", "murders", "were", "there", "in", "Britain", "last", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "How many great white sharks --", "answer_tokens": ["How", "many", "great", "white", "sharks", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "kill people every year but they're scared to swim?", "question_tokens": ["kill", "people", "every", "year", "but", "they", "'re", "scared", "to", "swim", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "gun", "murders", "were", "there", "in", "Britain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "A very low amount and I already went over those statistics.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "very", "low", "amount", "and", "I", "already", "went", "over", "those", "statistics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "How many, do you know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", ",", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "That was only a few hundred.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "only", "a", "few", "hundred", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "How many gun murders?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "gun", "murders", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "I actually, actually did pull up the statistics.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", ",", "actually", "did", "pull", "up", "the", "statistics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "I fled here?", "question_tokens": ["I", "fled", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Why don't you tell folks -- yes, you fled here.", "answer_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "tell", "folks", "--", "yes", ",", "you", "fled", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Why don't you go back and face the charges with the hacking scandal?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "go", "back", "and", "face", "the", "charges", "with", "the", "hacking", "scandal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Answer this question.", "answer_tokens": ["Answer", "this", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Why did you get fired from \"The Daily Mirror\" for putting on fake stories?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "get", "fired", "from", "``", "The", "Daily", "Mirror", "''", "for", "putting", "on", "fake", "stories", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "How many --", "answer_tokens": ["How", "many", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Do you know the answer?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "the", "answer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Do you understand the difference between 11,000 and 35?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "the", "difference", "between", "11,000", "and", "35", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Hey.", "answer_tokens": ["Hey", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Do you understand the difference?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "the", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Do you understand --", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "you", "understand", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "-- and 11,000?", "question_tokens": ["--", "and", "11,000", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "They know your script.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "know", "your", "script", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 179, "question": "You can pull those numbers up, OK?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "pull", "those", "numbers", "up", ",", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["-NONE-", "-NONE-", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Which weapon was predominantly used in the Aurora movie theater shooting?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "weapon", "was", "predominantly", "used", "in", "the", "Aurora", "movie", "theater", "shooting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "M-4 AR-15 variant.", "answer_tokens": ["M-4", "AR-15", "variant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Do you know that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Are we going to -- listen, why do you have the pilots have firearms?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "going", "to", "--", "listen", ",", "why", "do", "you", "have", "the", "pilots", "have", "firearms", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Let me ask you a second question.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "a", "second", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Do you know which weapon was used in the Oregon shopping mall mass shooting recently?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "which", "weapon", "was", "used", "in", "the", "Oregon", "shopping", "mall", "mass", "shooting", "recently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WDT", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "I understand that people who are mentally ill on all the serotonin reuptake inhibitors --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "understand", "that", "people", "who", "are", "mentally", "ill", "on", "all", "the", "serotonin", "reuptake", "inhibitors", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oregon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Do you know what the weapon used was?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "the", "weapon", "used", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Listen.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "Do you have a bodyguard?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "bodyguard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Alex.", "answer_tokens": ["Alex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Why do you have bodyguards?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "have", "bodyguards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "I don't have a bodyguard.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "bodyguard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Don't you want to protect your wife from hoodlums or you want to call the police?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "want", "to", "protect", "your", "wife", "from", "hoodlums", "or", "you", "want", "to", "call", "the", "police", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Let me ask you this question.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "this", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "-- to try and take Mr. And Mrs. America's guns?", "question_tokens": ["--", "to", "try", "and", "take", "Mr.", "And", "Mrs.", "America", "'s", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Don't be talking over me.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "be", "talking", "over", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. And Mrs. America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "What was the weapon used at Sandy Hook?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "weapon", "used", "at", "Sandy", "Hook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "I have already gone over that and already answered it for you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "already", "gone", "over", "that", "and", "already", "answered", "it", "for", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "What was the weapon?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "weapon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "It's a 223 M-4.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "223", "M-4", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "``", "VBZ", "''", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Are you seeing a pattern?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "seeing", "a", "pattern", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "People wouldn't go swimming because of the movie \"Jaws\" even though great white sharks kill five people a year.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "would", "n't", "go", "swimming", "because", "of", "the", "movie", "``", "Jaws", "''", "even", "though", "great", "white", "sharks", "kill", "five", "people", "a", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Why is the government arguing [inaudible] against this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "the", "government", "arguing", "[", "inaudible", "]", "against", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Why -- Alex. I don't --", "answer_tokens": ["Why", "--", "Alex.", "I", "do", "n't", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "ONES: What about \"Fast and Furious\"?", "question_tokens": ["ONES", ":", "What", "about", "``", "Fast", "and", "Furious", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "WP", "IN", "``", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Alex.", "answer_tokens": ["Alex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Alex."]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Why did our government ship guns to Mexico?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "our", "government", "ship", "guns", "to", "Mexico", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Calm down, Alex.", "answer_tokens": ["Calm", "down", ",", "Alex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mexico"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "To blame the Second Amendment?", "question_tokens": ["To", "blame", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Let's have a debate.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "have", "a", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 343, "question": "A false flag?", "question_tokens": ["A", "false", "flag", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Alex, I get accused --", "answer_tokens": ["Alex", ",", "I", "get", "accused", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 345, "question": "To blame the Second Amendment?", "question_tokens": ["To", "blame", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "I get accused --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "get", "accused", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex."]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Why did they blow up buildings down the street here in New York?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "they", "blow", "up", "buildings", "down", "the", "street", "here", "in", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Alex. Alex. I get accused when I get you guys on of talking over you, of being rude.", "answer_tokens": ["Alex.", "Alex.", "I", "get", "accused", "when", "I", "get", "you", "guys", "on", "of", "talking", "over", "you", ",", "of", "being", "rude", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "I'm trying to be civil, all right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "trying", "to", "be", "civil", ",", "all", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Alex, why do people need them?", "question_tokens": ["Alex", ",", "why", "do", "people", "need", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Go commit suicide by killing a bunch of kids and here's the gun to use --", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "commit", "suicide", "by", "killing", "a", "bunch", "of", "kids", "and", "here", "'s", "the", "gun", "to", "use", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Why do people need them?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "people", "need", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "They need them to protect us from the number one killer in history.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "need", "them", "to", "protect", "us", "from", "the", "number", "one", "killer", "in", "history", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "NNS", "RB", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "-- therefore have an AR-15 if they want one?", "question_tokens": ["--", "therefore", "have", "an", "AR-15", "if", "they", "want", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Statistically, where there's more guns there's lower crime.", "answer_tokens": ["Statistically", ",", "where", "there", "'s", "more", "guns", "there", "'s", "lower", "crime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Why don't you want to get rid of drugs, because they're half your sponsors?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "you", "want", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "drugs", ",", "because", "they", "'re", "half", "your", "sponsors", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Stick to the subject.", "answer_tokens": ["Stick", "to", "the", "subject", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Who do you believe was behind 9/11?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "believe", "was", "behind", "9/11", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Oh I absolutely know.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "I", "absolutely", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "But who do you believe was behind it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "who", "do", "you", "believe", "was", "behind", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "I have the proof.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "the", "proof", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS Radio"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Who, who, Alex?", "question_tokens": ["Who", ",", "who", ",", "Alex", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "WP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "They announced they blew up the towers on CBS Radio.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "announced", "they", "blew", "up", "the", "towers", "on", "CBS", "Radio", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Operation Gladio"], "LOCATION": ["Gulf of Tonkin"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Alex, who do you believe -- Alex, who do you believe was behind it, the American government?", "question_tokens": ["Alex", ",", "who", "do", "you", "believe", "--", "Alex", ",", "who", "do", "you", "believe", "was", "behind", "it", ",", "the", "American", "government", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Criminal elements of the military industrial complex, the same ones that staged Gulf of Tonkin, the same ones that staged operation, the mass shootings, Operation Gladio.", "answer_tokens": ["Criminal", "elements", "of", "the", "military", "industrial", "complex", ",", "the", "same", "ones", "that", "staged", "Gulf", "of", "Tonkin", ",", "the", "same", "ones", "that", "staged", "operation", ",", "the", "mass", "shootings", ",", "Operation", "Gladio", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Alex. Alex. Do you mean that President Bush and his administration were behind 9/11?", "question_tokens": ["Alex.", "Alex.", "Do", "you", "mean", "that", "President", "Bush", "and", "his", "administration", "were", "behind", "9/11", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "I mean that even mainstream news reported that the hijackers were ordered to be allowed into the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "that", "even", "mainstream", "news", "reported", "that", "the", "hijackers", "were", "ordered", "to", "be", "allowed", "into", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April 27th, 1933"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Germany"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "But is that what you believe?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "that", "what", "you", "believe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "The government -- Hitler fired bombs and turned rash tag, Piers, to bring in martial law in Germany, April 27th, 1933.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "government", "--", "Hitler", "fired", "bombs", "and", "turned", "rash", "tag", ",", "Piers", ",", "to", "bring", "in", "martial", "law", "in", "Germany", ",", "April", "27th", ",", "1933", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "How many guns do you own?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "guns", "do", "you", "own", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "I probably own more than 50 firearms.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "probably", "own", "more", "than", "50", "firearms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "What did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "It was disheartening, I think, you know I think just to see the anger there.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "disheartening", ",", "I", "think", ",", "you", "know", "I", "think", "just", "to", "see", "the", "anger", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "EX", "VBD", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", ":"], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "When our during the aftermath of ObamaCare when there were -- the president was being held in effigy and these kinds of threatening comments of people like the man you just had on were blocking members of Congress from being able to go and vote, you may recall of that, --", "answer_tokens": ["When", "our", "during", "the", "aftermath", "of", "ObamaCare", "when", "there", "were", "--", "the", "president", "was", "being", "held", "in", "effigy", "and", "these", "kinds", "of", "threatening", "comments", "of", "people", "like", "the", "man", "you", "just", "had", "on", "were", "blocking", "members", "of", "Congress", "from", "being", "able", "to", "go", "and", "vote", ",", "you", "may", "recall", "of", "that", ",", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "RB", "IN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Are you surprised that following the assassinations of John F. Kennedy, of Bobby Kennedy that we are in a position in America now where these kind of lawless mass shootings are happening with regularity and no one is doing much about it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "that", "following", "the", "assassinations", "of", "John", "F.", "Kennedy", ",", "of", "Bobby", "Kennedy", "that", "we", "are", "in", "a", "position", "in", "America", "now", "where", "these", "kind", "of", "lawless", "mass", "shootings", "are", "happening", "with", "regularity", "and", "no", "one", "is", "doing", "much", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Well, as I said, I think that the lack of discourse -- so that that is really what's offensive in our country where we should be able to debate our problems without impugning the integrity of the people who have positions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "I", "said", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "lack", "of", "discourse", "--", "so", "that", "that", "is", "really", "what", "'s", "offensive", "in", "our", "country", "where", "we", "should", "be", "able", "to", "debate", "our", "problems", "without", "impugning", "the", "integrity", "of", "the", "people", "who", "have", "positions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John F. Kennedy", "Bobby Kennedy"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Why did you agree to come back?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "agree", "to", "come", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Well, I thought maybe we could help you sell some more newspapers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "thought", "maybe", "we", "could", "help", "you", "sell", "some", "more", "newspapers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "More newspapers?", "question_tokens": ["More", "newspapers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Increase your viewership.", "answer_tokens": ["Increase", "your", "viewership", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "You're aware of that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "aware", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I'm sorry, yes, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", ",", "yes", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "If you were at the meeting with the Vice President Biden, with the NRA and Wal-Mart and others, what would you be saying?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "at", "the", "meeting", "with", "the", "Vice", "President", "Biden", ",", "with", "the", "NRA", "and", "Wal-Mart", "and", "others", ",", "what", "would", "you", "be", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "That the discussion has not been going anywhere that we can tell in a productive way.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "the", "discussion", "has", "not", "been", "going", "anywhere", "that", "we", "can", "tell", "in", "a", "productive", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA", "Wal-Mart"], "PERSON": ["Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Right, so your solution if you were there in that meeting would be to arm every school, every church, every hospital, everywhere that members of the public can be?", "question_tokens": ["Right", ",", "so", "your", "solution", "if", "you", "were", "there", "in", "that", "meeting", "would", "be", "to", "arm", "every", "school", ",", "every", "church", ",", "every", "hospital", ",", "everywhere", "that", "members", "of", "the", "public", "can", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "RATT: You certainly would want to encourage people who are qualified to carry a concealed firearm to be able to do so in a school zone.", "answer_tokens": ["RATT", ":", "You", "certainly", "would", "want", "to", "encourage", "people", "who", "are", "qualified", "to", "carry", "a", "concealed", "firearm", "to", "be", "able", "to", "do", "so", "in", "a", "school", "zone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Virginia"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "So why on earth would the fact that it's a gun free zone make any difference to them?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "on", "earth", "would", "the", "fact", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "gun", "free", "zone", "make", "any", "difference", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "IN", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "They're looking for -- it would seem in their sick minds to see if they can out-do the Virginia Tech slaughter, or some other thing that might be in their perverted minds.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "looking", "for", "--", "it", "would", "seem", "in", "their", "sick", "minds", "to", "see", "if", "they", "can", "out-do", "the", "Virginia", "Tech", "slaughter", ",", "or", "some", "other", "thing", "that", "might", "be", "in", "their", "perverted", "minds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Virginia Tech"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "So why should we give them a neon sign that says well, see if you can do better than the last guy over here?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "should", "we", "give", "them", "a", "neon", "sign", "that", "says", "well", ",", "see", "if", "you", "can", "do", "better", "than", "the", "last", "guy", "over", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "But you know there were armed security people at Virginia Tech.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "you", "know", "there", "were", "armed", "security", "people", "at", "Virginia", "Tech", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "My point to you, Mr. Pratt, is that even where you have a mass of well trained people and a mass of firearms, you can still have massacres, you'd accept that?", "question_tokens": ["My", "point", "to", "you", ",", "Mr.", "Pratt", ",", "is", "that", "even", "where", "you", "have", "a", "mass", "of", "well", "trained", "people", "and", "a", "mass", "of", "firearms", ",", "you", "can", "still", "have", "massacres", ",", "you", "'d", "accept", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Especially if you're telling the potential victim you can't be armed.", "answer_tokens": ["Especially", "if", "you", "'re", "telling", "the", "potential", "victim", "you", "ca", "n't", "be", "armed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "DT", ":", "RB", "CD", ",", "CC", "JJ", "-NONE-", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 660, "question": "Why do you know more about the impact and capability of the assault weapon than General McChrystal?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "know", "more", "about", "the", "impact", "and", "capability", "of", "the", "assault", "weapon", "than", "General", "McChrystal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "While the general was busy defending the country much of the time outside of the country, understandably he may not have noticed the Korean merchants who used an -- not one, but many AR-15 rifles with large magazines to defend themselves --", "answer_tokens": ["While", "the", "general", "was", "busy", "defending", "the", "country", "much", "of", "the", "time", "outside", "of", "the", "country", ",", "understandably", "he", "may", "not", "have", "noticed", "the", "Korean", "merchants", "who", "used", "an", "--", "not", "one", ",", "but", "many", "AR-15", "rifles", "with", "large", "magazines", "to", "defend", "themselves", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["General McChrystal"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "When was that, Mr. Pratt?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "that", ",", "Mr.", "Pratt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "-- against the mobs -- during the Los Angeles riots.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "against", "the", "mobs", "--", "during", "the", "Los", "Angeles", "riots", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "When was that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "That was some, what, 20 years ago.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "some", ",", "what", ",", "20", "years", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "Did you know how long ago that was, Mr. Pratt?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "how", "long", "ago", "that", "was", ",", "Mr.", "Pratt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "We're able -- let me finish my point if you would.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "able", "--", "let", "me", "finish", "my", "point", "if", "you", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "Why do you feel so strongly that civilians, despite what we just heard from a leading general, should still be able to have access to these killing machines?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "feel", "so", "strongly", "that", "civilians", ",", "despite", "what", "we", "just", "heard", "from", "a", "leading", "general", ",", "should", "still", "be", "able", "to", "have", "access", "to", "these", "killing", "machines", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "Well, because the general and his troops are not going to be there to protect the average American, the military nor the police after social order implodes, after a hurricane, after an earthquake, during riots.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "the", "general", "and", "his", "troops", "are", "not", "going", "to", "be", "there", "to", "protect", "the", "average", "American", ",", "the", "military", "nor", "the", "police", "after", "social", "order", "implodes", ",", "after", "a", "hurricane", ",", "after", "an", "earthquake", ",", "during", "riots", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Why do you still persist in trying to persuade Americans that the complete opposite is true?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "still", "persist", "in", "trying", "to", "persuade", "Americans", "that", "the", "complete", "opposite", "is", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "Well, first of all, according to your investigature (ph) of the constabulary, the data that you're using for the murder rate in England is a sham.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "according", "to", "your", "investigature", "(", "ph", ")", "of", "the", "constabulary", ",", "the", "data", "that", "you", "'re", "using", "for", "the", "murder", "rate", "in", "England", "is", "a", "sham", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "How long do you think it takes the police or a pathologist to count 50 bodies a year?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "do", "you", "think", "it", "takes", "the", "police", "or", "a", "pathologist", "to", "count", "50", "bodies", "a", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Go tell the Constabulary of Britain that they are lying.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "tell", "the", "Constabulary", "of", "Britain", "that", "they", "are", "lying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "That's what you're saying?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "That's exactly what your own Constabulary is saying.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "exactly", "what", "your", "own", "Constabulary", "is", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 747, "question": "Mr. Pratt, you are stating -- you are telling me on CNN we had how many gun murders last year?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Pratt", ",", "you", "are", "stating", "--", "you", "are", "telling", "me", "on", "CNN", "we", "had", "how", "many", "gun", "murders", "last", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 748, "answer": "Nine hundred seventy, and you have a violent crime rate that is the fourth highest in any country in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["Nine", "hundred", "seventy", ",", "and", "you", "have", "a", "violent", "crime", "rate", "that", "is", "the", "fourth", "highest", "in", "any", "country", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 778, "question": "What did you make of Mr. Jones' performance on the interview?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "Mr.", "Jones", "'", "performance", "on", "the", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 779, "answer": "Well, it seemed that you had improved your demeanor quite a bit from my own experience with you, and I congratulate you for maintaining it during that whole interview.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "seemed", "that", "you", "had", "improved", "your", "demeanor", "quite", "a", "bit", "from", "my", "own", "experience", "with", "you", ",", "and", "I", "congratulate", "you", "for", "maintaining", "it", "during", "that", "whole", "interview", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Jones"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "That's what our founders believed.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "our", "founders", "believed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "How many guns do you want in America, Mr. Pratt?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "guns", "do", "you", "want", "in", "America", ",", "Mr.", "Pratt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "That's not for me to decide.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "for", "me", "to", "decide", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Pratt"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "Do you think every American should have an AR-15?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "every", "American", "should", "have", "an", "AR-15", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "Every American should be able to get an AR-15.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "American", "should", "be", "able", "to", "get", "an", "AR-15", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 799, "question": "What are you going to do if President Obama wins his battle and brings in new stricter gun control legislation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "if", "President", "Obama", "wins", "his", "battle", "and", "brings", "in", "new", "stricter", "gun", "control", "legislation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 800, "answer": "Well, he's not going to do it by legislative, in my opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "do", "it", "by", "legislative", ",", "in", "my", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "George III"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 804, "question": "You're likening President Obama to George III?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "likening", "President", "Obama", "to", "George", "III", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 805, "answer": "Well, he -- President Obama hasn't banned the importation of ball and powder yet, which George III did, but that was one of the major contributory elements to our war for independence.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "--", "President", "Obama", "has", "n't", "banned", "the", "importation", "of", "ball", "and", "powder", "yet", ",", "which", "George", "III", "did", ",", "but", "that", "was", "one", "of", "the", "major", "contributory", "elements", "to", "our", "war", "for", "independence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "George III"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Where's the humanity in doing nothing after these massacres?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "'s", "the", "humanity", "in", "doing", "nothing", "after", "these", "massacres", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "The humanity was being able to do nothing during the massacre.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "humanity", "was", "being", "able", "to", "do", "nothing", "during", "the", "massacre", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 819, "question": "And you'd be happy with that if every school suddenly had people running around with guns, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'d", "be", "happy", "with", "that", "if", "every", "school", "suddenly", "had", "people", "running", "around", "with", "guns", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 820, "answer": "You're a good guesser, yes, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "good", "guesser", ",", "yes", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", ",", "CD", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "VBG", "NN", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WDT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 821, "question": "Where are they going to put them?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "they", "going", "to", "put", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 822, "answer": "Well, when people carry a concealed firearm, one doesn't exactly know for sure, and the element of surprise remains with the person carrying concealed, which means that somebody contemplating doing something horrible doesn't know which person or persons might be able to arrest him, to stop him, and that's why our jurisdictions that have easy access to concealed carry firearms enjoy lower murder rates than, say, the gun control Mecca of Chicago, which does better than one murder a day.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "when", "people", "carry", "a", "concealed", "firearm", ",", "one", "does", "n't", "exactly", "know", "for", "sure", ",", "and", "the", "element", "of", "surprise", "remains", "with", "the", "person", "carrying", "concealed", ",", "which", "means", "that", "somebody", "contemplating", "doing", "something", "horrible", "does", "n't", "know", "which", "person", "or", "persons", "might", "be", "able", "to", "arrest", "him", ",", "to", "stop", "him", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "why", "our", "jurisdictions", "that", "have", "easy", "access", "to", "concealed", "carry", "firearms", "enjoy", "lower", "murder", "rates", "than", ",", "say", ",", "the", "gun", "control", "Mecca", "of", "Chicago", ",", "which", "does", "better", "than", "one", "murder", "a", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 827, "question": "So I'm going to give you one more chance before we finish to say again how many gun murders you believed were in England and Wales in 2011?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "give", "you", "one", "more", "chance", "before", "we", "finish", "to", "say", "again", "how", "many", "gun", "murders", "you", "believed", "were", "in", "England", "and", "Wales", "in", "2011", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 828, "answer": "More important than the number of murders and it doesn't matter how a murder is committed, so I'm not going to really care about --", "answer_tokens": ["More", "important", "than", "the", "number", "of", "murders", "and", "it", "does", "n't", "matter", "how", "a", "murder", "is", "committed", ",", "so", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "really", "care", "about", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2011"], "LOCATION": ["England", "Wales"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130112pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 831, "question": "Can you repeat the number of gun murders that you said earlier?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "repeat", "the", "number", "of", "gun", "murders", "that", "you", "said", "earlier", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 832, "answer": "The data we have seen was 970.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "data", "we", "have", "seen", "was", "970", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]